<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE texts SYSTEM "../../../../dtd/ewdtext.dtd">
<texts lang="en" pubno="EM3140CG" style="font-size:6px;font-family:'Arial'" ver="2.1.2.6">
	<text textID="1">(The SRS is equipped with a back-up power source so that if work is started within 90 seconds from disconnecting</text>
	<text textID="2">* 1 :w/ TFT Display</text>
	<text textID="3">* 2 :w/o TFT Display</text>
	<text textID="4">* 7 :w/ Curtain Shield Airbag</text>
	<text textID="5">* 8 :w/o Curtain Shield Airbag</text>
	<text textID="6">* After work on the SRS is completed, check the SRS warning light.</text>
	<text textID="7">* Before repair, remove the airbag sensor if shocks are likely to be applied to the sensor during repair.</text>
	<text textID="8">* Center airbag sensor assembly</text>
	<text textID="9">* Curtain shield airbag assembly</text>
	<text textID="10">* Do not expose the following parts directly to hot air or flame;</text>
	<text textID="11">* Door side airbag sensor assembly</text>
	<text textID="12">* Even in cases of a minor collision where the SRS does not deploy, the following parts should be inspected;</text>
	<text textID="13">* For the purpose of reuse, never disassemble and repair the following parts.</text>
	<text textID="14">* Front airbag sensor assembly</text>
	<text textID="15">* Front passenger airbag assembly</text>
	<text textID="16">* If the following parts have been dropped, or have cracks, dents and other defects in their case, bracket,</text>
	<text textID="17">* If the vehicle is equipped with a mobile communication system, refer to the precaution in the IN section of the</text>
	<text textID="18">* Information labels are attached to the periphery of the SRS components. Follow the instructions of the notice.</text>
	<text textID="19">* Malfunction symptoms of the SRS are difficult to confirm, so the DTCs become the most important source of</text>
	<text textID="20">* Never use SRS parts from another vehicle. When replacing parts, replace with new parts.</text>
	<text textID="21">* Seat belt pretensioner</text>
	<text textID="22">* Side airbag assembly</text>
	<text textID="23">* Side airbag sensor assembly</text>
	<text textID="24">* Steering wheel pad</text>
	<text textID="25">* Use a volt/ohmmeter with high impedance (10 kΩ/V minimum) for troubleshooting electrical circuits of the system.</text>
	<text textID="26">* When the negative (-) terminal cable is disconnected from the battery, the memory of the clock and audio system</text>
	<text textID="27">* Work must be started more than 90 seconds after the ignition or starter switch assembly is turned to the "LOCK"</text>
	<text textID="28">Airbag ECU Assembly</text>
	<text textID="29">CAN Controller</text>
	<text textID="30">Combination Meter Assembly</text>
	<text textID="31">Curtain Shield Airbag Assembly LH</text>
	<text textID="32">Curtain Shield Airbag Assembly RH</text>
	<text textID="33">Driver Side Squib (Horn Button Assembly)</text>
	<text textID="34">Front Airbag Sensor LH</text>
	<text textID="35">Front Airbag Sensor RH</text>
	<text textID="36">Front Seat Airbag Assembly LH</text>
	<text textID="37">Front Seat Airbag Assembly RH</text>
	<text textID="38">Front Seat Outer Belt Assembly LH</text>
	<text textID="39">Front Seat Outer Belt Assembly RH</text>
	<text textID="40">Instrument Panel Passenger Airbag without Door Assembly</text>
	<text textID="41">LED Driver</text>
	<text textID="42">NOTICE :When inspecting or repairing the SRS, perform service in accordance with the following precautionary</text>
	<text textID="43">No. 1 CAN Junction Connector</text>
	<text textID="44">No. 2 CAN Junction Connector</text>
	<text textID="45">Pretensioner</text>
	<text textID="46">Rear Airbag Sensor LH</text>
	<text textID="47">Rear Airbag Sensor RH</text>
	<text textID="48">Rear Seat Outer Belt Assembly LH</text>
	<text textID="49">Rear Seat Outer Belt Assembly RH</text>
	<text textID="50">Repair Manual.</text>
	<text textID="51">Side Airbag Sensor Assembly LH</text>
	<text textID="52">Side Airbag Sensor Assembly RH</text>
	<text textID="53">Spiral Cable Sub-Assembly</text>
	<text textID="54">Spiral Cable Sub-Assembly , Driver Side Squib (Horn Button Assembly)</text>
	<text textID="55">finished, reset the audio systems as they were before and adjust the clock. Some vehicles have power tilt</text>
	<text textID="56">information when troubleshooting. When troubleshooting the SRS, always inspect the DTCs before disconnecting</text>
	<text textID="57">instructions and the procedure, and precautions in the Repair Manual applicable for the model year.</text>
	<text textID="58">memory function. However, it is not possible to make a record of these memory contents. So when the work is</text>
	<text textID="59">position (Ignition switch type) or the engine switch is pushed to the "OFF" position (Engine switch type)</text>
	<text textID="60">reset the memory. To avoid erasing the memory in each system, never use a back-up power supply from outside the</text>
	<text textID="61">the negative (-) terminal cable of the battery, the SRS may deploy.)</text>
	<text textID="62">will be cleared. So before starting work, make a record of the contents in the audio memory system. When work is</text>
</texts>
